// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = 
[
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Creating a password for any account must be:",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "All numbers",
      "Some special characters",
      "With capital letters",
      "All of the above"
    ]
 },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "You accidentally click the ad pop-up in the internet browser:",
    answer: "Install an ad blocker",
    options: [
      "Install an ad blocker",
      "Don't use the browser",
      "Just ignore the ads",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "There is a lot of friend request from strangers on your social media account:",
    answer: "Do not accept their request if you dont know the person",
    options: [
      "Only accept the request from good looking individual",
      "Do not accept their request if you dont know the person",
      "Create new social media account",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The most risky info to put in a social media account profile?",
    answer: "Address, Contact number, Financial information",
    options: [
      "Name, Age, Birthdate",
      "Nickname, Relationship status, Profession",
      "Address, Contact number, Financial information",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is first thing to consider when creating a post online?",
    answer: "Think before you click",
    options: [
      "Click before you think",
      "Do not post anything online",
      "Think before you click",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the best thing to do to identify a fake news?",
    answer: "Check the source, author, facts, comments and maintain a critical mindset",
    options: [
      "Check the source, author, facts, comments and maintain a critical mindset",
      "Every single thing on the internet is true and reliable.",
      "Just trust your own beliefs and instinct.",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What if someone asks for your IP address?",
    answer: "An IP address is not actually sensitive information but be careful with whom you share it.",
    options: [
      "IP Address is not that important because it is not your home address, you can provide it to anyone.",
      "Say no",
      "An IP address is not actually sensitive information but be careful with whom you share it.",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "There is an online friend who keeps harrassing you online, What would you do?",
    answer: "Stop all communication with the harasser, keep all evidence of harassment and report it to the police.",
    options: [
      "If it is good looking person then just give in, there is nothing to lose if it is online",
      "Stop all communication with the harasser, keep all evidence of harassment and report it to the police.",
      "Just kill the harasser",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "You see someone who impersonates you online:",
    answer: "Let your friends and parents know about this fake account and click the report button",
    options: [
      "Actually, that is an achievement you are so good looking person to have a poser account",
      "Let him/her feel your wrath then fight him/her in online conversation",
      "Ignore them",
      "Let your friends and parents know about this fake account and click the report button"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What to do when you receive a phising email?",
    answer: "Do not open the email and never click any links or download attachment that appear in the message",
    options: [
      "Do not open the email and never click any links or download attachment that appear in the message",
      "Open the email and click the available links out of curiousity",
      "Forward it to another person",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "A scheme that involves a message from a lottery company out of the blue, they claim to tell you you've won and/or recieved a grand prize in a lottery/competition you didn't enter",
    answer: "LOTTERY SCAM",
    options: [
      "LOTTERY SCAM",
      "INHERITANCE SCAM",
      "CARD SKIMMING",
      "LOVE/ROMANCE SCAM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "This scheme targets emotionally vulnerable people by making fake profiles on dating sites and social media",
    answer: "LOVE/ROMANCE SCAM",
    options: [ 
      "BOILER ROOM",
      "INHERITANCE SCAM",
      "LOVE/ROMANCE SCAM",
      "LOTTERY SCAM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The electronic posting of mean-spirited messages about a person often done anonymously",
    answer: "Cyber Bullying",
    options: [
      "Cyber Bullying",
      "Phishing",
      "Cyber Stalking",
      "BOILER ROOM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "This scheme that involves a message from someone out of the blue claiming you're a benifactor or heir to a wealthy person who has supposedly died without a will",
    answer: "INHERITANCE SCAM",
    options: [
      "CARD SKIMMING",
      "LOVE/ROMANCE SCAM",
      "INHERITANCE SCAM",
      "BOILER ROOM"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "false information that is spread, regardless of whether there is intent to mislead",
    answer: "Misinformation",
    options: [
      "Cyber Stalking",
      "Phishing",
      "CARD SKIMMING",
      "Misinformation"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];